
<plugin>
<title>Chelsea vs Leicester</title>
<info>Chelsea are only without January signing Ross Barkley, who is working towards full fitness and could play in the FA Cup third round replay with Norwich City next week.

Leicester City have Jamie Vardy available after a groin injury, but Wes Morgan and Danny Simpson (both thigh) remain unavailable.</info>
<link>
<sublink>http://kwesefta-i.akamaihd.net/hls/live/255186/FTA1/FTA1.m3u8|X-Forwarded-For=41.57.96.88</sublink>
<sublink>http://ukdvb1.uk.to:8085/NBCSN/mpegts?token=hcWUvw2Ur3</sublink>
<sublink>http://ukdvb1.uk.to:8085/NBCSN/mpegts?token=hcWUvw2Ur3</sublink>
<sublink>http://185.231.160.42/23/3/index.m3u8</sublink>
<sublink>plugin://plugin.video.SportsDevil/?mode=1&amp;item=catcher%3dstreams%26url=http://wizhdsports.fi/watch/Chelsea_vs_Leicester_City_live_Football/stream1</sublink></link>
<referer></referer>
<thumbnail>https://platform-static-files.s3.amazonaws.com/premierleague/badges/t8.svg</thumbnail>
<fanart></fanart>
</plugin>
<plugin>
<title>Crystal Palace vs Burnley</title>
<info>Andros Townsend and Jeffrey Schlupp (both ankle) have joined Crystal Palace's growing injury list. 

Mamadou Sakho (calf), Joel Ward (groin), Scott Dann and Jason Puncheon (both knee) are long-term absentees. Ruben Loftus-Cheek (knock) is doubtful. 

Loan signing Georges-Kevin Nkoudou will be part of the Burnley squad, Sean Dyche has confirmed.

Ben Mee (knock) should be fit but Chris Wood and Stephen Ward (both knee) are out and Scott Arfield (hamstring) is doubtful.</info>
<link>
<sublink></sublink>
<sublink>plugin://plugin.video.SportsDevil/?mode=1&amp;item=catcher%3dstreams%26url=http://wizhdsports.fi/watch/Crystal_Palace_vs_Burnley_live_Football/stream5</sublink></link>
<referer></referer>
<thumbnail></thumbnail>
<fanart></fanart>
</plugin>
<plugin>
<title>Huddersfield Town vs West Ham United</title>
<info>LatestSquadsStatsRelated
Match preview
Huddersfield Town's Collin Quaner (thigh), Chris Lowe (foot) and Martin Cranie (ankle) have been ruled out. 

Philip Billing and Michael Hefele are improving their fitness in training, says David Wagner, and January signing Terence Kongolo is in contention. 

West Ham United have doubts over Winston Reid, Andy Carroll and Michail Antonio. 

James Collins, Aaron Cresswell, Marko Arnautovic and Manuel Lanzini are back in training but it is unknown if they are fit to play.</info>
<link>
<sublink>plugin://plugin.video.SportsDevil/?mode=1&amp;item=catcher%3dstreams%26url=http://wizhdsports.fi/watch/Huddersfield_Town_vs_West_Ham_United_live_Football/stream3</sublink></link>
<referer></referer>
<thumbnail></thumbnail>
<fanart></fanart>
</plugin>
<plugin>
<title> Newcastle United vs Swansea City </title>
<info>Newcastle United captain Jamaal Lascelles has been passed fit and goalkeeper Rob Elliot is back in training. 

Florian Lejeune (foot), Jesus Gamez (ankle) and Aleksandar Mitrovic (back) are injured.

Swansea City have Leroy Fer available after the midfielder's appeal against a red card was successful, but defender Kyle Naughton is still suspended.

Angel Rangel (calf) is out and Renato Sanches (hamstring) and Tammy Abraham (hip) are doubtful. Ki Sung-yueng and Leon Britton are back in training and Connor Roberts could make a PL debut.</info>
<link>
<sublink>plugin://plugin.video.SportsDevil/?mode=1&amp;item=catcher%3dstreams%26url=http://wizhdsports.fi/watch/Newcastle_United_vs_Swansea_City_live_Football/stream4</sublink></link>
<referer></referer>
<thumbnail></thumbnail>
<fanart></fanart>
</plugin>
<plugin>
<title>Watford vs Southamptontitle>
<info>Liverpool could give a Premier League debut to January signing from Southampton Virgil van Dijk, while top scorer Mohamed Salah is fit after a groin strain.

Daniel Sturridge is back in training but Sunday will likely come too soon for Jordan Henderson (thigh) and Alberto Moreno (ankle).

Manchester City are without captain Vincent Kompany and Gabriel Jesus, though the latter could be fit within two to three weeks.</info>
<link>
<sublink>plugin://plugin.video.SportsDevil/?mode=1&amp;item=catcher%3dstreams%26url=http://wizhdsports.fi/watch/Watford_vs_Southampton_live_Football/stream2</sublink></link>
<referer></referer>
<thumbnail></thumbnail>
<fanart></fanart>
</plugin>
<plugin>
<title> West Bromwich Albion vs Brighton - Hove Albion</title>
<info>West Bromwich Albion do not expect to have James Morrison (calf) and Nacer Chadli (thigh) available for another four to five weeks. 

Alan Pardew says the rest of his players are all fit, with Jonny Evans set to play.

Brighton & Hove Albion are without loanee Izzy Brown, who has returned to parent club Chelsea due to a torn anterior cruciate knee ligament. 

Steve Sidwell has sustained an ankle injury in addition to a back problem and is not expected to be available within the next few months.</info>
<link>
<sublink>plugin://plugin.video.SportsDevil/?mode=1&amp;item=catcher%3dstreams%26url=http://wizhdsports.fi/watch/West_Bromwich_Albion_vs_Brighton_-_Hove_Albion_live_Football/stream6</sublink></link>
<referer></referer>
<thumbnail></thumbnail>
<fanart></fanart>
</plugin>
